EUAN CAMPBELL

First Class BSc in Computer Science

With a keen interest in developing practical and usable solutions to ambitious projects, I relish the opportunity to tackle new challenges surrounding software development and equivalent fields. With experience in dealing with various technology stacks, I enjoy dealing with applications used in for financial services.

EXPERIENCE

Production System Support Team, Octopus Labs, London

O Application Support Analyst / Apr 2019 – Present

A more prominent role was taken on within the 6 person team, creating custom-built software with Python to monitor our applications to spot issues faster. Also continued my normal role of finding and correcting any issues across company applications used both internally and by customers. Issues could take anywhere between 10 minutes and several months to correct, ensuring effective solutions were found each time.

O Graduate Application Support Analyst / Aug 2018 – Apr 2019

Understanding how industry software is created and maintained, working with desktop and web applications to allow Octopus Investments to manage over 100,000 portfolios, while ensuring data was proper maintained.

Tutor/Proctor, Coventry University / Sep 2016 – Jan 2018

Teaching first year Computer Science students, working with 30-40 students to help with their group projects involving robotics and programming.

Guangzhou University, China / Apr 2017

A two week visit to experience both the culture of China and engage with students also studying computer science. A project was conducted in groups, of which ours was voted best by a panel of ambassadors from both our university and theirs.

EDUCATION

Computer Science BSc, Coventry University / Sep 2015 – Jul 2018

First-Class Honours

With a focus on practical applications in industry, commerce, research and everyday life, students study a combination of theory and practice in traditional areas of computer science, including programming and algorithms, computer architecture, networking, system design and implementation. We also look into some of the new and exciting areas of development in this ever-changing field, such as machine learning, artificial intelligence, data science techniques, mobile app development and cryptography in software security.

PROJECTS

System Monitor

Monitoring at Octopus Labs was limited, with our teams morning checks consisting of just a PowerShell script. I set out to formalise the monitoring of our applications by developing a modularised Python platform, allowing us to add on additional modules for future functionality. Modules varied from monitoring database tables to checking specific services were running at the correct times.

Pathfinding Algorithm

github.com/euanacampbell/Pathfinding-Algorithm

Starting as a side-track from a university group project and later being used for my dissertation, this pathfinding algorithm uses techniques from Dijkstra's Algorithm and A-Star as a method for determining a route. Results are promising, showing improvements particularly in efficiency.

PERSONAL INFO

Soi

South East London



07977055774

 \times

euan.campbell.personal@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO



euancampbell.info



linkedin.com/in/euancampbell



github.com/euanacampbell

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Management

- lira
- Agile Scrum
- Git/Version Control
- · Visual Studio Team Services

Other

- · Scripting with Python and PowerShell
- Microservices
- Metastorm Designer
- SQL Server Management
- Google Cloud Platform
- Visual Studio Code
- Adobe Illustrator / Photoshop
 - CAD and Laser Cutter
 - Template Design
- Windows / Linux Ubuntu / macOS

REFERENCES

References are available upon request.